Guide to the Love Makes a Family Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Audiovisual Recordings and Photographs, 2001-2009; Series II
  - Photographs
    - Electronic, Computer files.
      - Circa 2002-2009
        Consists of digital photographs maintained by LMF on a shared drive and on photograph management sites. The photographs within each folder are organized by event.
        - BoxNet
        - GoDaddy
        - Photos (from shared drive)
      - Celebrate the Love, 2005 October 01
      - Civil Union Today: Marriage Equality Tomorrow forum, 2005 November 16
        Photographs by Bill Hensley.
      - Eat, Drink and Be Married gala, Wadsworth Antheneum Hartford, Connecticut, 2006 April 8
      - Anne Stanback induction to Connecticut Women's Hall of Fame, 2006 October
      - Eat, Drink and Be Married, 2006
      - Open Hearts Cafe with Mary Taylor benefit concert, 2007 March 31
        Concert held at the United Methodist Church in Milford, Connecticut.
      - Holly Near event, 2007
        Photographs by Ellen Grusse.
      - Marriage Makes a Word of Difference premieres
        - Unknown location, 2008 January 20
        - New Haven, New Britain, Norwalk, [2008]
      - Vote "No" American Music to Support the CT Constitution, [2008]
    - Print
      - Eat, Drink and Be Married gala, Westport, Connecticut, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 1-2)
        Photographs by Tim Coffey.
      - Rally for Marriage Equality at the Capitol in Hartford, Connecticut, 2004 May 17 (Box 90, Folder 3-5)
- Website and Social Media Sites, 2009-2010; Series III
  The Website and Social Media Sites series is arranged in five sections: ConvioWebsite, Website (Final), Facebook, Twitter, and YouTube. The files, copies from the original sites, document LMF's public representation and interactions from circa 2004 to 2009. Of particular note are the ConvioWebsite files, which include copies of multiple versions of the Web site, emails to members, and action alerts.
  - ConvioWebsite, Computer files.
    Consists of copies of LMF Website content from Convio, LMF's Web service provider. The files consist of action alerts (AA); stylesheets (CSS); documents (DS); event calendar information (EC); LMF emails sent from Convio; forms; images; java script (JS); photo albums (PS); PageBuilder pages (PB); archived versions of each web page (PB versions); StoryBuilder content (SB); and surveys.
    - AA, 2009-2010
      Consists of Advocacy Action Alerts. Includes file "0000 Event Calendar Filename Key.xls" with links to each action alert.
    - CSS, 2009
      Consists of stylesheets for Website.
    - DS, 2009
      Includes documents that were included in the Website.
    - EC, 2009
      Consists of Event Calendar files. Includes file "0000 Evenet Calendar Filename Key.xls" with links to each event, event date, and title.
    - Email, 2009
      Consists of all LMF emails sent through Convio.
    - Forms, 2009
    - Images, 2009-2010
    - JS, 2009
      Consists of javascript used in the Website.
    - PA, 2009
      Consists of Covio hosted photograph albums.
    - PB, 2009
      Consists of final (full) version of the LMF Website. The home page and the entire Website can be accessed by clicking on "home.html". Includes "0000 PageBuilder Pages Filename Key.xls" with links to each page.
    - PB versions, 2009
      Consists of "archived" versions of the LMF Website.
    - SB, 2009
      Consists of news clips and press releases. Includes "0000 Story Builder Filename Key.xls" with links to content, published date and title.
    - Surveys, 2009
  - Website (Final), 2009-2010; Computer files.
    Consists of the final LMF Website homepage.
  - Facebook, 2009; Computer files.
  - Twitter, 2009; Computer files.
  - YouTube, 2009; Computer files.
    Consists of moving image files added to YouTube and linked to the LMF website.